<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<HashingInfo>
  <HashAlgo Type="SHA1">
    <Description>
      <blockquote>
        In cryptography, SHA-1 is a cryptographic hash function designed by the National Security Agency and published by the NIST as a U.S. Federal Information Processing Standard. SHA stands for Secure Hash Algorithm. The three SHA algorithms are structured differently and are distinguished as SHA-0, SHA-1, and SHA-2. SHA-1 is very similar to SHA-0, but corrects an error in the original SHA hash specification that led to significant weaknesses. The SHA-0 algorithm was not adopted by many applications. SHA-2 on the other hand significantly differs from the SHA-1 hash function. SHA-1 is the most widely used of the existing SHA hash functions, and is employed in several widely-used security applications and protocols. In 2005, security flaws were identified in SHA-1, namely that a mathematical weakness might exist, indicating that a stronger hash function would be desirable. Although no successful attacks have yet been reported on the SHA-2 variants, they are algorithmically similar to SHA-1 and so efforts are underway to develop improved alternatives. A new hash standard, SHA-3, is currently under development — an ongoing NIST hash function competition is scheduled to end with the selection of a winning function in 2012.
      </blockquote>
      <li>
        It produces 160-bit hash values.
      </li>
    </Description>

  </HashAlgo>
  <HashAlgo Type="SHA256">
    <Description>
      <blockquote>
        SHA256 was designed by NIST and is the US
        federal standard for hash functions, specified in
        FIPS-180 (1993).
      </blockquote>
      <li>
        It produces 160-bit hash values.
      </li>
    </Description>


  </HashAlgo>

  <HashAlgo Type="SHA512">
    <Description>
      <blockquote>
        SHA512 was designed by NIST and is the US
        federal standard for hash functions, specified in
        FIPS-180 (1993).
      </blockquote>
      <li>
        It produces 160-bit hash values.
      </li>
    </Description>

  </HashAlgo>
</HashingInfo>
